The
I don't know.
Thanks for teaching me how to do this, Gojo.
You're seriously my hero.
No problem.
I wanted to make sure the ribbons were in the right place, so it worked out.
But I'm really sorry that you didn't get to go to the festival with your dad.
Why are you sorry?
He's the one who canceled on me.
But I'm glad at least you have a soul.
Homework?
Of course I haven't done it.
I still have two whole weeks of summer vacay left.
What?
What are you talking about?
That's plenty of time.
Wait.
We're not going because of homework that's not even due yet!
Yeah, that was a real thing I went through.
Not sure why he wouldn't believe me since I'm the one who actually goes there.
He's been asking me to send pics of my homework as proof that I'm doing it.
That's micromanaging, warden.
This totally sucks.
I haven't gone to a single festival this year.
Almost forgot.
Iwatsuki had their fireworks festival yesterday.
What?
And you didn't even think to invite me?
Worst friend ever.
Well, you couldn't go anyway because of your homework.
Okay, fine.
I've been out there busting A on a bunch of jobs I got.
So I guess I just blocked the whole summer homework thing out.
That reminds me.
I've been wanting to ask what it is you do for work.
Oh, you know.
Just stuff.
See?
What?
Seriously?
Kizakawa, you're in a magazine!
Are you like a new celebrity I hadn't heard about?
No, I'm a model.
Mostly just catalog.
How did that happen?
I was at the salon and this one editor thought I had a good look or something
and asked if I was interested.
I said, sure, why not?
It's cool.
I've just been doing way more shoots than usual lately.
Oh.
Oh, that almost doesn't look like you.
What an amazing shot.
Right?
It's because I've got an actual makeup artist beating my face.
So why are you doing so many additional shoots lately?
You're exhausted.
Well, DSLRs are top dollar.
Gotta write that check.
Oh, uh, Kitagawa's seriously planning on buying one of those mega expensive cameras?
Ugh, I call break time.
Ooh, do you feel like watching a movie?
You really like watching scary movies, don't you?
Like's a strong word.
More like FOMO since part three's coming out.
I want to know what all the hype's about.
Plus, it's what you do in summer.
Okay.
I don't usually watch horror films, so...
How scary are these exactly?
Well, it's just a movie, so it won't be that scary.
You can do it.
I believe in you.
What?
A voicemail?
Who could it be from?
Oh, hello.
Let me see your eyes.
Turn around.
I'm right behind you.
Oh, no, stop, please.
Why are you doing this to me?
Stop it.
No.
Wow, what an ending.
That was a great movie.
Meh.
It was okay.
But it wasn't scary like at all, though.
There was one scene that was brilliant.
You don't mind if we watch it again, right?
Why would we do that?
Maybe I can figure out how they did their costumes and special effects makeup.
I mean, check out that fabric.
It looks old, yeah?
And do you think they're using contact lenses?
It's probably CG.
Look at that.
Oh, cool.
There's so much to learn from each scene.
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Okay, Dad.
Here's some homework picks for ya.
And donezo!
Ah, that was rough.
If there was math, too, I couldn't handle it.
We have math.
But I already finished mine, though.
Wait, what?
But I don't have my...
I'm seriously gonna die.
I think I left everything at school!
They weren't happy that we showed up out of uniform, huh?
I'm so sorry I made you come with me.
It's fine. It's on my way home anyway.
I'm just glad you found your assignments.
Yeah, but seriously, the school looks hella creepy after watching that movie, doesn't it?
It's so dark and spooky.
Not to mention our footsteps are echoing.
If we got here any later, this would have been a full-blown test of courage.
That's true.
Oh, I need to go get some things to make dinner.
I know. How about you eat with us tonight?
Really? I thought you'd never ask me again.
I'm pretty sure she's only been eating that sad fried rice.
So, what you got on the menu?
I was thinking some cold somen noodles with some shrimp, onion, and mitsuba kakiage.
Oh my god, that sounds amazing!
I can't believe you can make a kakiage.
You've got some mad skills, Chef Gojo.
I can't fry anything to save my life.
That's like expert level.
Huh?
Ooh!
I never took swim class, so I haven't gotten a chance to check out this butte.
It's ginormous up close!
I don't know if it's such a good idea for us to be here when we're not on the swim team.
I'm sure regular students are allowed.
I gotta dip my feet in for real!
Testing.
I don't think you should do that!
Just let me try it!
KiteZa!
KiteGaw!
Thanks, bro. I seriously thought I was a goner.
Yeah, so did I. Do you really not know how to swim?
Not, dude. Can't even float. It just looks so nice and cool.
Wait a minute. Didn't you say you went to the beach with your friends around the beginning of the month?
Did you actually have fun?
You mean because I don't swim?
Yes.
I don't mind missing out on that part.
I basically just go to the beach to eat, hang out, and take pics.
So that's how my socks are rocked.
Oh, I can see that.
It's so nice.
I love sitting on the sand, listening to the crashing waves,
and I love watching the ocean get sparkly when the sun starts to set behind it.
It's really magical, you know?
Even if I can't swim, I always jump at the chance to go.
I'm sure that must sound a little crazy to you, huh?
Like, who does that?
What's funny? What did I say?
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
It's not crazy.
I understand you.
I feel the same way.
Even though I still can't paint Hina dolls very well,
I love them.
It's fun.
Exactly.
That's totally what I mean.
I'm sure we all feel that way about something.
I agree.
But not being able to swim could lead to drowning,
so let's not take it that far.
Yeah, I promise I'll be more careful.
Hey, Gojo?
Yes?
Thank you.
I'm gonna look for festivals that are still happening.
Wanna come if I find one?
But what about homework?
You still have a lot to do.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Okay, I'll finish the rest super fast.
Just help me with the hard parts.
Sure, you've got it.
I'm so proud of Maureen for finishing all her homework.
Yeah.
Okay, see ya.
Right.
You be careful out there.
Have a great time, Wakana.
There are so many people.
I didn't know it got this crowded.
Man, it's gonna be tough for her to find me in this mess.
Where is she?
I hope she's okay.
There he is!
I finally found you!
I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
The crowds here are crazy, so I had a hard time getting through.
It's cool.
You're wearing your new clothes!
See, I told you they'd look great on you.
Who's high?
Thanks.
And you decided to wear a yukata?
Yep.
I went all out and had someone do my hair and get me into this thing.
What's wrong?
Oh, I think I know.
You're a back-of-the-neck dude, aren't ya?
Wait, what?
Um, well, uh, I wouldn't say that.
Uh, uh...
No way!
For real?
For really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really?
I couldn't choke on how hyped I am right now!
I'm so glad I wore a yukata!
I'm death-dropping neck bombs out here!
So, any idea what time the fireworks show starts?
Are you excited or angry right now?
Look, they have candy apples there!
I'm going in!
Everything here looks great!
Oh, okonomiyaki!
Thank you!
This looks amazing!
Kitagawa!
Huh?
They have yakitori, too!
Nice and hot!
Right.
We're not done yet!
This is a lot of food!
Had to get enough for two people!
Wow!
Let's go slam it down in the plaza!
Thank you for your patience!
We're excited to announce that the fireworks show will start momentarily!
Please enjoy!
Crap!
We better hurry up, Gojo!
Right!
You know, this is actually my first time coming down to the plaza to watch the fireworks!
Seriously?
No way!
You never went to the fireworks festival at Iwatsuki?
That's sort of a waste when you live so close, isn't it?
Harry Potterese?
Sure!
You never run away!
You have to get to theola in theтver.
i can smell the gunpowder and the smoke i can hear people cheering
seeing everything so close feeling these sounds resonate through my whole body
last year the year before and even before that every year that i can remember i'd be alone in
my room fireworks were just some loud echoing noise i'd hear off in the distance
but this year it's different
on YouTube
on a
Thank you!
Your tongue's blue!
What happened? Are you dying right now?
I ate a blue Hawaii, Goober! It turns your tongue blue!
And you ate it knowing that?
Yup! Look at it! Look at it!
Gross! Stop!
The straps did a number on your feet. You must be in so much pain.
There's a convenience store nearby. I'll go get you some bandages.
Nah, no point going there just to come all the way back.
But you're hurt.
I'm not dead, so just take me with you.
Take you how?
Look how high are you!
Is this what your life is like? I'm so jealous of your giraffe view!
She smells really nice.
But for real, how tall are you?
Um, 180, I guess?
Stagawa, it's dangerous if you move too much!
Whoops, my bad. I figured you'd be about that tall.
The last part of the fireworks was out of control!
They were beautiful.
Pretty funny that you can't see them in the smoke.
Yeah, I didn't know that could happen.
I'm happy that I came.
Me too. Well, mostly anyway.
Kinda lame that my shoes decided to become piranhas in the end.
What jerks.
You're not used to wearing them, so it makes sense.
I know, but when this sort of crap happens, it sucks the life out of the day you were having and leaves you with a weird sense of meh.
So, I'm sorry, Gojo.
I promise that I'll be more careful next year.
She said next year.
Oh, and next year, we should go to Iwatsuki's fireworks festival, too!
Yeah, let's do it!
Actually, why don't we just hit up all the fireworks festivals in the Kanto region?
Really? You think we could do that?
You can do anything with the right attitude.
And someone to help carry you.
I don't know.
If you want if you don't feel trustworthy, I don't hurt you.
Either way!
アートがふわふわふわふわ
いけない ふっかり 見とれちゃう
過ぎ過ぎてどうしよう
自分自身に正直に
だからね お願い
綺麗になってく私を
近くで見てた
I guess it's time to call it a night.
Hey, Kitagawa. Everything okay?
Hey, Gojo. What are you doing right now?
I'm going to bed. It's pretty late. Did something happen?
Well, no. I mean, not exactly.
I... I was just thinking of you and wanted to hear your voice.
So I'm sort of afraid to go to sleep!
I ended up watching All in Den 2.
Oh, that's the sequel, right?
But wait, didn't you say you weren't scared of that movie?
Yeah, but that was just because you were over here with me that time, so I was mostly fine with it.
But I'm by myself now and every little sound is freaking me out.
I would seriously die if someone came up behind me, so I've been on high alert.
I took a shower and didn't shut my eyes once.
What? Come on, I'm sure nobody's there. Besides, it's a fictional plot, right?
You don't know that for sure, Gojo. Could be a true story. You ever thought about that?
Like, what if there's a zombie voicemail on my phone right now and I get murdered?
I seriously came with all this? I just watched a movie about smartphones and now I have a voicemail and there's nothing I can do about it.
Please, Gojo. It doesn't have to be for long. I just need you to keep talking to me.
You can even put your phone on speaker and fall asleep.
Um, okay, sure.
So, that's what happened.
How is Noah so super strong?
That girl is unreal.
I had no idea she was like that. Crazy.
Ah, you know, I feel like I'm not as scared anymore.
Thanks for being a boss, Gojo.
I'm glad it helped. I'm sure you're tired.
I can't believe school starts tomorrow.
It's not fair. Summer vacay was way too short.
There's still so much I didn't get to do.
Like watch Prez Host.
Do a little more modeling.
Oh, and I wish we'd gone to one more cosplay event together.
There's not enough time in one day.
Right.
One day.
Sounds like he's about to pass out.
I think this year was really fun.
Mm-hmm.
It was.
We did so much together.
Every day has been so amazing.
Hey, Gojo.
I love you.
He's out like a light.
Well, that was pointless.
I should try to sleep too.
I'm gonna hang up.
Okay, Gojo?
Good night, Cooper.
See you later.
I'll be right back.